[Music]
hey guys we're at CES 2019 and our first
stop is the Alcatel booth and they've
got two new phones they want to show off
to us this is the Alcatel one see in the
Alcatel 1x and you've probably heard
that name before that's because they're
just refreshing them for 2019 making
them a little bit better updating some
software updating a little bit of the
hardware so yeah we got the 1c here
that's gonna be the starter version and
it's running Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition
so it's got one gig of ram so it's runs
that easier version of Oreo that is
easier on the processor and it's running
a spectrum processor that's not a
processor we hear that often a lot of
these phones while the One X is running
a mediatek processor so it's a little
more high-end so the of tell 1c has got
a 5-inch display with an 18 by 9 aspect
ratio the interesting thing about this
phone is that it's 3g only so this is
definitely gonna be for the emerging
markets the people that just like need
to get a phone and need to have a smart
phone because you can do most things on
a smart phone as long as you have one
it's got a 5 megapixel camera on the
back and it's also got a headphone jack
so if you want a headphone jack not a
bad option to get as a media player and
then the One X which is the higher-end
model of this phone is got a 5.5 inch
display with an 18 by 9 aspect ratio is
wearing the full version of Android 8.1
Oreo and it's got what is essentially a
13 megapixel camera but you've got two
cameras on the back here so you can get
that bokeh mode that selfie mode so just
gonna be a little bit more expensive
Alcatel told me that this is gonna be
under a hundred and twenty dollars so
for people that just like need to get a
very cheap smartphone but want maybe a
little upgrade over the one seat this is
gonna be a good pick up so we have an
article down below where we detail these
completely in full with all the
different specs and everything this is
just a quick look we just wanted to show
you some b-roll show you a little first
look at these things so I'll see you in
the next video
[Music]